This is my bug out phone.
This is the Alcatel WP61 Plus. It is the
most massive and impressive phone I've
ever seen. And it comes with its own
antenna. You want to know why? Because
communication is not Wi-Fi dependent
with the professional DMR walkie-talkie.
3.4 mile range. Pretty cool. You just
touch to talk. Breaker breaker 1-9. This
is the phone [music] you want when the
grid goes down. The battery on this at
20,000 milliamps is worth more than
this, this, and this put together. It's
basically indestructible.
>> [music]
>> I mean, indestructible.
>> [clears throat]
>> Takes a licking keeps on ticking. I bet
you've never hosed off your phone to
clean it. I spend a lot of time under
houses and need a good light. This right
here is a spotlight, not a flashlight.
[music]
Yeah, a little fixing to do on here. The
camera is insane at 108 megapixels. An
iPhone only has 48 megapixels. But what
makes it insane is the night vision.
[music] The storage is out of this
world, too. This is 16 gigabytes cost
1,700 bucks. This 512 gigabytes
expandable to 2 terabytes and cost 519
bucks. This is my bug out van. This is
my bug out plan. Alcatel WP61.
Emergency, flashlight, power bank,
everything for when the grid goes down.